ZINEB LEGHNIDER

AWS CLOUD ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

A highly dynamic and driven graduate with BSc Psychology degree from the University of Warwick. Currently working toward achieving the AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification, undergoing an AWS re/Start programme. Always taking a dedicated and resilient approach toward any task faced, or challenge presented with. An excellent collaborator who naturally finds themselves in a leadership position. Keen to delve into a career in DevOps, applying both practical experience and strong academic background to tackle the process of developing and deploying effective cloud solutions.

INTERESTS

- Internet of Things, Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning
- Human-Computer Interaction, specifically UX/UI design
- Health, fitness and wellbeing, particularly powerlifting
- Traveling and experiencing different cultures

CONTACT INFORMATION

Notting Hill, London, W2

- Email: zineb.leghnider@icloud.com
- Mobile: +447747612253
- LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/zinebleghnider

REFERENCES

Available upon request.

EDUCATION

Generation UK & Ireland

AWS re/Start | Sept 2020 to Nov 2020

- A 12-week intensive bootcamp covering in-demand technical skills required to become a successful cloud computing engineer.
- Areas covered across the program include:
 - Linux administration (Bash shell scripting)
 - Networks
 - Security
 - Databases (SQL)
 - Python
 - AWS Services (such as EC2, S3, Lambda, EBS, RDS, DynamoDB, VPC, CloudFront, IAM and more).

University of Warwick

BSc Psychology (Hons) | 2016 to 2020

- Graduated with a 2.1 (67% overall) and achieved a First in a dissertation research project (82%)
- Took part in an exchange programme at Monash University, Australia (2018-19), gaining valuable global experience.
- Extracurricular: Founded Warwick DubaiSoc, a member of Warwick Lacrosse, Taekwondo, LINE Fashion Society, Arabic Society and Moroccan Society.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Educator

lululemon athletica [AU/UK] | Aug 2018 to Oct 2019

- A team member of the highest volume store in Australia and New Zealand, and a member of the London Marylebone team, being able to juggle many tasks
- Providing numerous guests with a word-class education on our product and our company's promises, values and culture.
- A member of the inventory body, with an extensive knowledge of product, back of house operations and allocations.

Bar and Hospitality Staff

Flair Events | Jul 2017 to Present

- A member of the front-of-house bar team for a number of large scale events including sporting events and festivals.
- Maintaining a high standard of service in a high pressure environment, working alongside team members to serve large crowds
- Ensuring payments are handled safely and securely.

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

IT Skills:

- AWS infrastructure configuration and deployment
- Web Development (HTML and CSS)
- Linux Administration
- Python and JavaScript
- SQL and NoSQL databases
- Adobe Photoshop

Personal Skills:

- Languages spoken: Arabic (fluent) and Spanish (intermediate)
- Team work and collaboration
- Problem solving and analysis
- Confidence in leadership and public speaking